IBRAHIM MOHAMMED

JUNIOR DATA SCIENTIST

Personal Profile

I am a junior Data Scientist that has specialized in the design and implementing of analytical systems to extract meaningful information from large amounts of data. My passion for machine learning and AI drives my pursuit for knowledge. My aim is to better the lives of Africans through Data Science and technology.

Job Experience

UMUZI ORG

DEC 2018 - PRESENT

Junior Data Scientist

- Learning to become a data scientist
- Do data science projects to improve my skills and for my portfolio
- Help with communication between managers and recruits

SEESAYDO

Jan 2014- Aug 2015

Intern

- Support with the co-ordination of events, workshops, brainstorms, launches
- Right hand to all operational activities
- General admin- upkeep of databases, templates, checklists, process flows

TECHNICAL EXPERTISE

- Python
- SQL
- JavaScript
- Html
- CSS

You can contact me at:

Mobile: 0619917727

Ibrahim.mohammed@umuzi.org

github.com/lbby19

Education

UMUZI ACADEMY - DEC 2018

- NQF Level 5 Certificate in Systems development
- Data Science Curriculum

ROSEBANK COLLEGE - 2016 (NOT FINISHED)

- Diploma in IT Network Management

HOLY FAMILY COLLEGE - 2009 TO 2013

- National Senior Certificate

